Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Why you can't imagine being lost until a single minute.
It's fun!
The day begins early for a magic night, there is much to be done before the sun goes down.
There is cleaning, laundry, my heart belongs to Sister Lily and I won't betray her for anybody!
Ahhhh!
Next!
Tending to the Beasts
Sit, Beastie!
Yeah, good boy! I think you've earned a treat. Go on.
Feeding them even if it turns out you're on the menu for breakfast. And then...
Hey, Captain Yami! Captain!
The unbelievable task of waking up Yami Sukihiro, Captain of the Black Bulls.
Captain, sir! It's morning!
Shut up now or I will kill you!
Yes, sir! Sorry, sir!
You're the one who told me to wake you up every morning!
It is also a magic night's duty to put up with the whims of their sometimes fickle captain.
Another day of backbreaking manual labor. Being in a magic night squad is a lot more work than I expected.
How is this any different from what I did back at the church? What does a magic night squad do?
First thing in the morning, meat, meat, and more meat.
Hey, Noelle! How come you don't ever help out with the cleaning and stuff?
The cleaning? I'm royalty, you know.
And a new recruit!
I've never done any cleaning or laundry in my life. Why would I start now?
Are you bragging about being lazy? Come on, we're on the same squad here! Ever heard the term team effort?
I am royalty!
Yeah, and you won't let us forget it!
Silence, insect!
We're back to that?
Hey, uh, just wondering, what exactly does a magic night squad do?
Huh?
Are you seriously serious right now?
We protect the country, you idiot! Keep the people safe! It's the manliest job in the world!
Why'd you even want to join up if you were so freakin' clueless, huh?
Well, answer me!
I'm sorry, I just wanted to be done with the video!
Why did you even take the exam if you don't know what we do?
Well, those two are certainly chipper, aren't they?
Anybody? Anybody?
Anybody?
No?
This one!
This is the kind of idiot!
You stupid dick coming to our turf without a clue!
I don't know how to do!
I don't know how to do that!
Geez!
Will someone tell him what a magic night squad does?
How about you, wino?
Well, uh, we like safeguard the citizens' safety!
You know, that sort of thing.
And as a bonus, you can get to know some marvelous gentlemen while you're on guard duty.
Oh, okay!
Hmm.
Well, if you ask me, the best part's all the people you get to fight!
You can spend hours beating up a criminal and nobody will even think twice about it!
More than anything, it's an excellent career.
One that makes my sister proud.
See her?
Marie?
I use my wages to buy her nice things.
Remember, if you lay a finger on her, then you die!
Okay, and what about you?
Saving women left and right, making all of them want you.
What more could you ask for?
I can tell you right anymore, you're scared because we're friends.
What's wrong, Charmy?
How did this happen?
This is awful!
The food is off!
It's all gone!
I'm nowhere near full!
Cotton creation magic!
Bring on the sheep hooks!
All right!
That's more like it!
The most important thing is when you're in a magic night squad, you can eat like crazy!
Ah!
Munch, munch!
Gray?
Well, it's just a good job, you know?
A clone?
I'm really looking forward to our first mission together.
Uh, yeah.
Man, there are some serious weirdos in this place.
What am I doing?
They're insane!
Should I even be in this squad?
Watch closely.
You take this, and you do this, and now it's yummy!
So very yummy!
Here, you take a bite!
Go on!
I can't!
I'm way too full!
Really!
Well, runt!
Are you starting to understand what being a magic knight is all about?
Oh, come on!
Just mistake you!
No!
Not even a little bit!
I'm coming for a moment.
It's not true!
Okay.
You Schwab.
Maher.
Magna, we're going!
Yes, yummy, sir.
What's going on?
There's a mission.
A real Magic Knight squad mission.
Hold on!
I'll come to!
No way.
Can't bring a kid along.
This is an important mission.
Only grown-up men allowed.
Okay, we'll be back.
Bye.
Listen, gang.
No breaking stuff while we're gone.
Okay.
Have fun. Bye.
Captain, will you fight me when you get back, pretty please?
Don't be having too long, Captain.
I'll be waiting for you.
Hurry back.
You don't want to go together, do you?
I don't know how much longer I can wait to see Marie.
I'm going through withdrawal.
I'd like to hit on...
I mean, get on a mission, too.
Really? What am I doing here?
Captain Yami's going, and he's taking Magna.
They both looked so serious.
What kind of mission is this?
Oh, man.
This is bad, all right.
Totally, seriously, crazy bad.
From the looks of it, the two of you are done for.
Flush!
Two pair.
Nothing.
She got us, sir.
That'll never get old.
I lost it all.
That was over half a year's wages.
It's a pleasure, Magna.
Always.
You too, Captain.
I'll be able to buy a lot of nice souvenirs for the village.
Deal us in for one more hand.
Really, sir?
Hey, now.
You have nothing left to wager.
Not even underwear.
It's true.
He took everything we had.
No, not yet.
Here's my offer.
One last hand.
That's all.
If we win, then you give us back everything.
Oh.
All right.
And what if you lose?
Your prize.
You're kidding, right, sir?
Well, Gramps, what do you say?
Please.
You can't bet that and you know it.
He's right.
Come on, Captain.
Shut it!
This is where we push our limits.
I'm not so sure about this.
Hey, here's an idea.
You lose to me, and you have to do any one thing I say.
Well?
Anything.
What?
Are you crazy?
Yami would never agree to that kind of-
Kind works.
Yami agrees to the terms of the wager!
Come on, Sehi, let's do this!
Say your prayers.
Ha!
I don't think I'm the one here who needs to be praying.
Yeah.
These'll do.
I don't think I'm the one here who's a good beastie.
Let's see him.
Okay.
There, there.
Who's a good beastie?
Meat treat?
Don't you stand there, help me!
Do I look like I feed animals?
You're lucky I even came down here.
You should be thanking me.
That's not gonna happen!
I thought I was dead for sure.
You truly are very strong.
That's because I train hard!
That hand!
Captain Yami!
I didn't see it coming!
Magna!
So then, the mission must be-
That old man, he actually pulled out a royal flush.
Incredible!
Should have known.
We didn't stand a chance against old Sehi.
He was motivated to beat us today, that's for damn sure.
Hey there, Rasta!
No, no.
We're back!
Guess what?
I got some news I think you're gonna like.
It's time for your first mission.
Like I said, we've decided to put you in the field.
Alright, our first mission.
Here we go.
So, what are we doing?
I assume it's something befitting royalties such as myself?
Yeah!
It's a real honor.
Go to Saucy Village for some boar hunting.
Huh?
Hunting boar?
Boink!
Well, that is a terrible mission.
No, it's not!
You take that back!
I can break down a boar with my bare hands!
Easy!
No, you can't!
Don't even think about trying!
Those things are pure evil!
They got beady eyes, huge tusks, and they charge for no reason!
We lost to the chief of Saucy Village.
Now we gotta pay the price.
Huh?
The two of you lost in a fight?
That doesn't even seem possible!
How powerful was this man?
We lost at poker.
At poker?
He literally stripped us of everything we had.
Including half a year's wages.
Really?
Why would you brag about that?
That's not all.
We also promised we'd do any one thing he requested of us.
And that turned out to be getting rid of some boar.
There's been a herd of them hanging around near the village.
Trampling fields and causing trouble.
Well, I'll head back and wait for you there.
Oh, here, you can have these back at least.
Can you explain what this has to do with us?
Yes, exactly.
You were the ones who lost.
It was none of our doing.
So why-
You idiots!
Do you seriously expect Yami to clean up his own mess?
Oh, yeah.
It seems reasonable.
Yami doesn't deal with these things.
That's what he's got us for.
Either go or die.
Your choice.
We'll go!
So what if it's boar hunting?
We're finally going on a mission!
I'm getting pumped now!
Yeah!
I still don't see why you would be sending me-
Come on!
Do you ever do anything but complain?
Actually, that wasn't intended as a complaint.
It's just...
Given that I can't control my magic power,
should I really be going on a mission at all-
Dummy!
That's the whole point!
How do you expect to get any better if you aren't even willing to try?
And besides, we're not sending some wet-behind-the-ears recruits out there alone.
I'll be around to keep an eye on you two.
Whoa!
You're such a madly man, Magna!
Ah, enough of that, Rasta.
I'm blushing.
Well, if you insist, I suppose I would be willing to accompany you.
Really?
Wow, thank you.
Hey, wait a minute!
How come you're always looking down on us, huh?
It isn't that I choose to look down on you.
You just always happen to be below me, so what else can I do?
What kind of logic is that?
Do your thing!
Use your spatial magic to send us to Saucy Village.
Saucy Village?
No can do.
Come on, it's not like I'm asking a lot-
Now, now.
I can go to distant places,
but only if I've marked them with my magic power before.
Huh?
In other words,
you want to go somewhere I've never been?
Sorry, can't do it.
Well, that was a waste of time.
Fine, I'll have to go by broom, then.
Um, Magnus, sir!
Yeah, what is it?
I can't fly on a broom!
Um...
Yeah, what is it?
What he said.
Are you two kidding me?!
You're so completely incompetent that you can't manage something that freaking simple!
Oh, you're pretty much the most basic skill of me has!
I don't have any magic power, remember?
Why do you look so proud?
And since I can't control my magic power,
a broom is out of the question.
Obviously.
And why are you being so arrogant?
Fine!
We'll just have to ride together.
Are you ready to meet my baby?
Your baby?
Here it is!
Introducing Crazy Cyclone!
I know, right?
Awesome, isn't it?
Yeah!
Way awesome!
Try lame.
Excuse me?
Are you so blind that you can't even recognize beauty when you're staring right at it?
It's lame!
Oh...
You can't do it, can you?
A man never goes back on his word!
Let's do this thing!
FRIVE!
Woo-hoo!
There, you see?
Crazy Cyclone does just fine, even with three riders!
Careful!
Are you certain you've flown this thing before?
Whoa, newbie!
Try not to get so clingy!
Silence, you mohawk punk!
Now's not the time for name-calling!
Oh, yeah!
This is amazing, Magna!
We're one with the wind!
Rasta!
You trying to die or something?
Hold on!
Right!
Hey, watch where you put your hands, insect!
What the hell are you doing?
Back there!
RAAAARRRGH!
Right on time!
Huh?
Oh, no!
Shh!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
So it's here, is it?
The magic stone?
Find it.
Sir!
In the mist, be lost.
The magic stone?
I'll stop on.
We think that the strength is so crazy.
It's strange, but if you want to laugh, it's okay to laugh.
What I want to do is what I want to do.
I want to see the same morning.
I want to choose the next day.
That's my crazy cyclone!
Way cool, huh?
Actually, between you two, I'd say your head is the crazy cyclone.
Who are you calling a cyclone?
But the crazy part's fine.
We came for some boar hunting, but wound up facing much deadlier game.
I won't let them get away with making everyone suffer!
Black Clover, page nine.
Beasts!
My magic is never giving up!